visible.com 2019-05-20

# Visible | Privacy Policy

#### Effective Date: April 23, 2018

Visible values your business and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies and practices for the collection, use and sharing of your information. Visible is a member of the Verizon family of companies. 

#### I. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

We collect information when you visit our websites, use our apps, contact us, and when you subscribe to and use our wireless service. 

**We collect information you provide directly to us.**  This includes personal information (such as your name, email address, phone number, postal address, Social Security number, and date of birth), a username and password, payment information, and communications you send to us. 

**We collect information when you use our service.**  This includes information about the calls you make and receive, text messages you send and receive, websites you visit, mobile applications you use, and wireless network and device information, including location, Internet protocol (IP) address and connection speed, mobile telephone number, device and advertising identifiers, browser type, and operating system. 

**We also collect information when you visit our sites and use our apps, including through cookies and similar technology.**  This includes your IP address, device and advertising identifiers, browser type, operating system, pages that you visit before and after visiting our sites, the date and time of your visit, information about the links you click and pages you view within the sites, and other standard server log information. 

We may use cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies to automatically collect this information. Cookies are small bits of information that are stored by your computer’s web browser. Pixel tags are very small ../images or small pieces of data embedded in ../images, also known as “web beacons” or “clear GIFs,” that can recognize cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device. By using our websites and applications, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies. 

**We collect info when you contact us.**  When you contact us or we contact you, we may monitor or record that communication for quality assurance, training and security purposes. 

**We collect information about you from others.**  We may obtain information about you from other sources, including from companies that collect consumer information such as demographic and interest data. In addition, if you access third-party services, such as Facebook, Google, or Twitter, from our sites or apps, to log into our sites or apps, or to share information about your experience, we may collect information from these third-party services. 

#### II.    USE OF INFORMATION

We use the information we collect to deliver service, to market to you, and for other business purposes. 

  * We use the information we collect to:
  * Fulfill your requests for products, services, information and customer support; 
  * Determine products and services that may interest you and market them to you; 
  * Analyze the use of the sites, apps, and service for our purposes, such as product and service enhancements; 
  * Research and develop new products and services;
  * Authenticate you;
  * Customize the content you see when you use our sites and apps; 
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and otherwise in accordance with our Terms of Use; and 
  * For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or with your consent. 

#### III. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We share information about you with vendors and partners who do work on our behalf and for other business purposes. We may also share certain information about you with affiliates for marketing. 

  * **Authorized service providers and partners.**  We share your information with service providers and partners that help us with a variety of things, including development and delivery of our sites, apps and service. This includes services provided by others to help us with analytics which may include storing and accessing cookies and other information on your computer or wireless device. 
  * **Affiliates.**  We share customer information with our affiliates, including the [Verizon](https://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/privacy-policy-summary) and [Oath](https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/index.html) family of companies, for a variety of purposes, including, for example, providing you with the latest information about our products and services and offering you our latest promotions. You can limit the sharing of certain types of customer information, known as Customer Proprietary Network Information, or CPNI, within the Verizon family of companies for marketing services to you that are different from your current Visible services. See “Your Choices,” below. 
  * **Business transfers.**  We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. 
  * **Legal purposes.**  We may disclose information (1) to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims or government inquiries and in emergencies such as those involving the danger of death or serious injury to any person; (2) to advance, protect or defend the rights, interests, property, safety, and security of Visible, our affiliates, users, or the public; (3) to identify, protect against, and address unauthorized or unlawful use of our sites, apps or service, or our network; and (4) to outside auditors and regulators. 
  * **Collections.**  We may disclose information to collection agencies to obtain payment for Visible-billed products and services. 
  * **Aggregated and De-identified Information.**  We may aggregate or otherwise de-identify information and use it for our own purposes or share it with third parties for their own purposes. 
  * **With your consent.**  We may share information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect the information or pursuant to your consent. 

If you access third-party services, such as Facebook, Google, or Twitter, through our sites or apps, to log in or to share information about your experience with others, these third-party services may be able to collect information about you and they may notify your connections on the third-party services about your use of the site or app, in accordance with their own privacy policies. 

#### IV.    SECURITY

We use reasonable measures to help protect information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You should understand that no data storage system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. 

We use reasonable measures to help protect information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You should understand that no data storage system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. 

#### V. YOUR CHOICES

You have choices about certain ways we use and share information about you. 

**Customer Proprietary Network Information.  **Visible customers may choose to limit the use and sharing of Customer Propriety Network Information (or “CPNI”) among Visible’s affiliates, which includes the Verizon family of companies, for the purpose of marketing communications-related services that are different from those you currently have. CPNI is information that relates to the type, quantity, destination, technical configuration, location, amount of use and related billing information of your telecommunications or interconnected Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) services. Federal law governs our use and sharing of CPNI. Notice about Visible’s use and sharing of CPNI and the choices you have may be provided in your monthly statement or in other ways. To opt out, log in to your account and go to “Privacy” in your Account in the Visible app or online at www.visible.com/account/privacy. 

**Marketing.  **You have choices about receiving marketing from Visible. If you would like to be removed from Visible’s email marketing list, you can opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions, usually found at the bottom of the emails. 

**Cookies.  **You may be able to refuse or disable cookies by adjusting your web browser settings. Because each web browser is different, please consult the instructions provided by your web browser (typically in the “help” section). If you choose to refuse, disable, or delete these technologies, some of the functionality of our apps or sites may no longer be available to you. 

**Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms.  **Some web browsers transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. We currently do not take action in response to these signals. 

#### VI.    CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

We are required to disclose information, upon request, to our California customers and to allow California residents under age 18 who are registered users to request removal of information they have publicly posted. 

A business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83 is required to disclose to its California customers, upon request, the identity of any third parties to whom the business has disclosed personal information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Please note that under California law, businesses are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year. 

A business subject to California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 must allow California residents under age 18 who are registered users of online sites, services or applications to request and obtain removal of content or information they have publicly posted. Your request should include a detailed description of the specific content or information to be removed. Please be aware that your request does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of content or information posted online and that the law may not permit or require removal in certain circumstances. You can contact us by email at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com "Follow link"). 

#### VII. INTERNATIONAL USERS

Our sites, apps and service are designed for and targeted to U.S. audiences and are governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the U.S. We make no representation that our apps, sites or service are operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of any other nation. By using our apps, sites or service and providing us with information, you understand and agree that your information may be transferred to and stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and, to the extent you are a resident of a country other than the United States, that you consent to the transfer of such data to the United States for processing by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### VIII. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we update the Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Effective Date” date above and post the new Privacy Policy. 

#### IX. STILL HAVE QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us at [privacy@visible.com](mailto:privacy@visible.com "Follow link"). 

© 2019 Visible Service LLC
